Guide to the Douglas C. Engelbart Papers M0638
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2. Accession 1998-094
  - Alphabetical Files, 1962-1991
    - Alpha Files E-R 1973
      - NCC Del Frames, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      - Net Dialog, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 42)
      - Networks, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 43)
      - Newcastle, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 44)
      - NIC, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 45)
      - NIE, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 46)
      - NSF, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 47)
      - NLS (oN-Line System) File Structure, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 48)
      - NP (Needs & Possibilities), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 49)
      - NPL Scrapbook System, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 50)
      - NRC Canada, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 51)
      - NSF, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - NSN, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - NLS Command Language Changes, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - SRC & ARC O&M, NP, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Old Log, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - People & Places, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Planning, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - POST, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Plato, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Proceedings, CCC, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Programs, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Prom Contact Log, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Proposals, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Rech, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Reference Papers, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Resource Data, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Resource Sharing, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Alpha Files S-Z 1973
      - Sample Journal Items, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Slides, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - Smithsonian, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - SPF, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - SRI, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Structural Programming References, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Subject Bibliography General, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Synergy, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - Trade Intelligence, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - Tree Meta, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 24)
      - Trip Reports, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - U Illinois, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 26)
      - U Sussex, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 27)
      - Washington, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 28)
      - Workshop, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Alpha Files A-M 1974
      - Misc. Unfiled, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 30)
      - McIntosh, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 31)
      - Bootstrap, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 33)
      - AHI, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 34)
      - AI & NLS, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 35)
      - Alphacom, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 36)
      - AMC, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 37)
      - ANET-ARC, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 38)
      - ARC, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 39)
      - Army T&E Agency, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 40)
      - ASME, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 41)
      - ARPA, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 42)
      - BC, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 43)
      - CAD, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 44)
      - CML, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 45)
      - Command Language, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 46)
      - Comindex, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 47)
      - Communications, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 48)
      - Current Action, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 49)
      - DEIS, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 50)
      - DOT, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 51)
      - ET Progs, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 52)
      - Economic & Technological Feasibility, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 53)
      - European Liason, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 54)
      - FFRY, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 55)
      - Forms, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 56)
      - Graphics, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 57)
      - Grist, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 58)
      - Guidelines, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 59)
      - Incentives, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 60)
      - Industrial Automation, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 61)
      - Information Analysis Centers, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 62)
      - Interchanges with McCarthy, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 63)
      - Inter-Environmental Protocol, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 64)
      - IPTO, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 65)
      - Journal, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 66)
      - Kirk, John, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 67)
      - Knowledge Work, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 68)
      - LIO, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 69)
      - Mail & Phone, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 70)
      - MFRMT Program, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 71)
      - Messages, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 72)
      - MST Features, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 73)
      - Multi Host Journal, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 74)
      - Museum Data Bank Coordinating Committee, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 75)
    - Alpha Files N-Z 1974
      - NASA, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - NDM, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - NIC-SYS NP, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - NLS, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - NP, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - NSF, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - NTMS, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Online Calendar, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - ONR, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - P Notes, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Plan, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Poparad, JT, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Printour Frames, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - Prog-Pilot, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - Prom, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - RECOL, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 16)
      - Research, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - Scholar-NLS, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - 1974 (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - Scratch, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - Slide Catalog, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - Study of a National Center..., 1974 (Box 42, Folder 21)
      - Sys Dev Methodology, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - Take/Do, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - Tasker System, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 24)
      - Terms, Editors, Etc., 1974 (Box 42, Folder 25)
      - Transparencies, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 26)
      - Util, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 27)
      - Washington Itinerary, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 28)
      - Watson, WA, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 29)
      - West Point, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 30)
      - WP-CAD-E, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 31)
      - Workstation Equipment, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Alpha Files A-C 1975
      - Journal Citation, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 33)
      - Lit Search, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 34)
      - Misc. Unfiled, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 35)
      - Addresses, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 36)
      - AKW, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 37)
      - AML, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 38)
      - ANET Transition, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 39)
      - Applications, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 40)
      - ARC, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 41)
      - Architect, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 42)
      - ARPA, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 43)
      - BC, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 44)
      - Backend Transfer, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 45)
      - Boehm, Barry, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 46)
      - Bonneville Power, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 47)
      - Brazil, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 48)
      - Business Mode, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 49)
      - CIT Format, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 50)
      - CML, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 51)
      - CNRC, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 52)
      - Collaborative Support Systems, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 53)
      - Computer Assisted Research, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 54)
      - Contacts, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 55)
      - Copeland, John, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 56)
      - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 57)
      - Cost of Hardware, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 58)
    - Alpha Files D-T 1975
      - OBMS Interface, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - DCA, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Development, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - DEX, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Display Generator, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - DoD, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - DPCS, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - DPS, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Enslow, Phil, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - ETS, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Ext-to-ARC, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 19)
      - FAA, DOI, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - Facility Proficiency Experiment, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 21)
      - Fe-Be Economics, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - FMS, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Formatters, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - Forms, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 25)
      - Frame/DPS, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 26)
      - GE, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 27)
      - Graphics, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 28)
      - Human Capacity, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - Hyphenation, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 30)
      - Information International, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 31)
      - Jersey, Bill, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 33)
      - Journal, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 34)
      - KWAC, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 35)
      - Langley Porter Clinic, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 36)
      - Lawrence Hall of Science, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 37)
      - Logicon, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 38)
      - LP, Cluster, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 39)
      - LRPS, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 40)
      - McIntosh, Stuart, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 41)
      - M, New, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 42)
      - Mail Service Committee, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 43)
      - Mailsys, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 44)
      - Margins, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 45)
      - Marketing, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 46)
      - Message Format, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 47)
      - MGRP, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 48)
      - MIT, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 49)
      - MITRE, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 50)
      - Mod-to-Features, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 51)
      - Monterrey Institute, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 52)
      - More Grist, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 53)
      - Morgan, Howard, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 54)
      - Multi-Host Printer, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 55)
      - Ned Business Arrangement, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 56)
      - Nelson, Ted, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 57)
      - NL Performance, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 58)
      - NLS, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 59)
      - NP, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 60)
      - NSW, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 61)
      - Office of the Future, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 62)
      - Org Dev, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 63)
      - PCP, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 64)
      - Phone, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 65)
      - Planit, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 66)
      - Prog, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 67)
      - Propst, Bob, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 68)
      - Process Commands Upgrade, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 69)
      - Quirk & WUC, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 70)
      - Quotations, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 71)
      - RADC, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Readmail, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - References, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Requirements Management, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - S List, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Saltzer, Ben, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Sharing Tech Info, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Slides, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - SRI, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Tabs, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Tech Disc, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Teleconference & AKW, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Text Adressing, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Alpha Files D-S 1976
      - Dialog Support, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 55)
      - Distributed Programming System, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 56)
      - Doc Dev, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 57)
      - DPCS, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 58)
      - DPS, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 59)
      - Drucker, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 60)
      - EDUCOM, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 61)
      - File Structure, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 62)
      - Electro-Optical & OSIS, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 63)
      - Electrostatic Printer, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 64)
      - Elements, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 65)
      - ERIC, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 66)
      - Ericsson, LM, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 67)
      - EST, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 68)
      - Ethernet, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 69)
      - Far West Lab, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 70)
      - First National City Bank of NY, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 71)
      - Grist, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Heavy-Line Graphic Mode, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Help System, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - IEEE, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Inter-System Debugger, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Introduction to DNLS, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - IPTO-NELC, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Journal, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - KWAC, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Large Files, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Law, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Letter Template, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - McIntosh, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Macros, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Mail Systems, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Managing Organizational Change, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - MENSA, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - MSL, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Museum Data Banks, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - NDRE, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Nestle, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Net Refs, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Newsletter, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - NIP-NSF, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - NIH, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - NLS, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Norway, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - NP, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - NSA, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - NSF, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Office 1, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - O&M NP, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - Outlook for Computer Mail, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 33)
      - Output to Printer, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - Paisley/Butler, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - Personal Communication Skills, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 36)
      - Plan for NSF Office, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 37)
      - RADC, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 38)
      - References, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 39)
      - Retreival, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 40)
      - Samuelson, Kjell, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 41)
      - Science Letter, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 42)
      - SINFDOC Presentation, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 43)
      - Slides, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 44)
      - Smithsonian, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 45)
      - Social Security Administration, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 46)
      - SRI, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 47)
      - Augment Manuals
        - MDC CGM (Box 26, Folder 9)
        - DEC System 20 User Guide (Box 26, Folder 10)
        - Augment Engine Training (Box 26, Folder 11)
        - TENEX User Guide (Box 26, Folder 12)
        - IFIP, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Alpha Files S-Z 1976
      - Strategies for Human Use..., 1976 (Box 19, Folder 40)
      - Subscribers, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 41)
      - SWEDCO, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 42)
      - Sweden, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 43)
      - Technological Development Corp., 1976 (Box 19, Folder 44)
      - Video Display, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 45)
      - Word Processing, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 46)
      - World Problem, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 47)
      - Evans, D. A. Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Alpha Files A-K 1977
      - Misc. Unfiled, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 49)
      - Aerospace, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 50)
      - AIEE, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 51)
      - AKW, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 52)
      - ARC, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 53)
      - ARPA, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 54)
      - ARPANET, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 55)
      - Basic, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 56)
      - Bootstrap Community Clippings, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 57)
      - Bechtel, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 58)
      - Bennett, John, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 59)
      - BIFOA, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 60)
      - CAD/CAM, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 61)
      - Command Sequence Processsing, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 62)
      - Communication of Federal Paperwork, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 63)
      - Computer Mail, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 64)
      - Consistent Tool Interface, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 65)
      - Consult/Office Automation, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 66)
      - CONTACT, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 67)
      - Cotton, Ira, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 68)
      - DARCOM, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - DCA, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Design/Network Facility, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Dialnet, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - ECOM, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Electronic Mail, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Ergonomics, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Elite, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Ericsson, LM, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - External Re: SEAS, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Evaluation of Project 42732, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Floating Point, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - FMS, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Fortune, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Giulana, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Grist, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Hardy, Martin, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Harrenstein, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - HC Interface, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Human Communication Through Computers, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - IEEE, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Impact, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Info Mapping, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 23)
      - Intellectual Augmentation, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - Interactive Tools, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - Interests, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 26)
      - KWAC, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Alpha Files L-Z 1977
      - Ledgard, Henry, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 39)
      - Market Grist, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 40)
      - Misc. System NP, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 41)
      - Management Software Development, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 42)
      - MIS N-W, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 43)
      - MIT, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 44)
      - NPS, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 45)
      - NBS, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 46)
      - New Devices, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 47)
      - NLS, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 48)
      - NMA, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 49)
      - NP, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 50)
      - NSA, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 51)
      - N-10, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 52)
      - Org Dev at ARC, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Optimizing, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - P-Note, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Personal Productivity, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - P-Org NP, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Presentation Outline, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Prodev, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Professional Reading, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Programming, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Proposals, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Query Locator, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - RADC, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - ROM Template, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Reenskarg, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - SAFE, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Small Computer Design, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - SRI/AIC LIFER Manual, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - SV-IE, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Subsystems, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Technical Support - Elite, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - TNET, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - TNLS Primer, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - UNIVAC, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 23)
      - Video Terminal System, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 24)
      - Visits, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 25)
      - Viewing Knowledge..., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 26)
      - Word Processing, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 27)
      - XD, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 28)
      - Commercial Seminars, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 29)
      - NP-Basic, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 30)
      - NP Work, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 31)
      - T Plan, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 32)
      - Misc. Unfiled, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Alpha Files A-O 1979
      - Misc. Unfiled, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - ACT, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - ARC Augment Specs, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - APP A Clippings, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Augment Development Targets, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - B Files, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - BIFOA, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - Bigelow, Ed, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Clarkson, Max, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Consensor, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Crocker, D., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Data Dictionary, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Decision Support, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - Diebold, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Display Products, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - EOP, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - E Prop, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Essay Draft, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - External People, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Farber, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Fast Search, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Framework, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - GMP, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Grist, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Hi Performance, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - HPAT, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - IBM, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - IFIP, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Imperial Group, Ltd., 1979 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Initial Des./Super Docs, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Institute for Synergy in Action, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Kvaerner, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Language, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Lantz, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - LOC, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Lonex Extracts, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - LR Talk, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Mail System Design, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - Memo Form, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Man/Computer Communication, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - Mouse Collection, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - MSE Group, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Multichannel Memo Transmission, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - Multimedia, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - NBS, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 32)
      - NL Citation Maintenance, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 33)
      - NLS 10, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 34)
      - NP, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 35)
      - NSF, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 36)
      - NSRDC, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 37)
      - Online Citation Maintenance, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 38)
      - Oregon State University, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Alpha Files H-Z 1980
      - High Performance Application, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - Hiltz, Roxanne, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 18)
      - How to Use a Long Screen, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 19)
      - HP, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 20)
      - HPAT Dev Prog, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 21)
      - Human Engineering Lab, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 22)
      - IEEE, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 23)
      - Information Management, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 24)
      - Internet MSS Protocol, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 25)
      - IRDT, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 26)
      - JAIMS, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 27)
      - Johansen, Bob, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 28)
      - Journal, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 29)
      - Layout, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 30)
      - Library Committee, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 31)
      - Lodahl, Tom, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 32)
      - Mail System, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 33)
      - Malibu Electronics, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 34)
      - Marcus, Jane, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 35)
      - Mini-Aug, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 36)
      - MSG Surveys, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 37)
      - McCaffrey, Sue, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 38)
      - NCC-80, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 39)
      - NDM Publics, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 40)
      - NL Work, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 41)
      - Norway, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 42)
      - OAD, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 43)
      - OPCP, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 44)
      - Plan Notes, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 45)
      - Polytext, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 46)
      - Printer Control, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 47)
      - Proctor & Gamble, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 48)
      - PSL/PSA, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 49)
      - Public Networks, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 50)
      - RADC, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 51)
      - Ralston, Anthony, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 52)
      - Relevant Help, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 53)
      - SHARE, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 54)
      - Shepard, Bob, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 55)
      - Speech Products, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 56)
      - SRI/AIC, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 57)
      - Stefferud, Eina, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 58)
      - Steward, Donald, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 59)
      - STP Questionaire, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 60)
      - Super Micro Workstations, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 61)
      - TD, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 62)
      - Textual Applications Group, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 63)
      - TNIX, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 64)
      - TS, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 65)
      - Typesetting, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 66)
      - Unifying Tymshare Family, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 67)
      - U of Texas, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 68)
      - UMshare, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 69)
      - Wohlgethan, June, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 70)
      - XDOC, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 71)
      - Zavala, Albert, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 72)
      - Misc. Unfiled, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 73)
    - Alpha Files A-Z 1981
      - AC SRC Proposal, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 82)
      - Airmics, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 83)
      - Apple, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 84)
      - ARPA, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 85)
      - Bair, James H., 1981 (Box 36, Folder 86)